your own folder, so that is what you find. Then you can go into the startup kit, startup package,
startup package again, and then you will find here the template abstract final thesis
and this document, this one we need for the registration. So you will find here,
for example, you have to write down the title, fill it here with motivation and half a page of
packages and structure with bullet points. So that is what we need for the registration.
And what we also need is, I don't know the English word, so the registration formula.
That is also something you find online.
And if you do that, we can start with the registration. Or what? Exactly. Sorry,
I do not understand the question. Can you maybe frame it a little bit different or show me what
you mean? Abstract. So the formulation for the registration, so it's the German word is
Fassungspogen, so formulae of, I don't know the English word. Fassung, maybe you can ask one of
your colleagues. Nevertheless, I can also send you, but I guess you will also find it
in the startup package, but I'm not sure. Let me have a look. Where is it? I guess it's that one.
I will cut it directly. Give me a second. So you need this document here, this one here,
a Fassungspogen. I don't know, maybe there is also an English version of that. So a Fassungspogen,
and you have also write down here your name, street and all the stuff that is for bachelor
thesis, but you also will find that for master thesis, but you have to look online. So I named
it here Fassungspogen RWTH. So maybe I will send you here the word in German, and then you have,
yeah, should be, yes, should be English, but German is also fine. So both, I guess English
is a little bit easier for you. So you can also do that in a German version, but it's both okay.
So we need the abstract two sides, and also we need the Fassungspogen, and that's it.
Then we can start the registration. Yes, perfect. Then do you have more questions?
Yes. Thank you. See you. Bye-bye. Not next week, the week after. No, no, not next week,
the week after. Perfect. See you. Bye-bye.